Ichi-chan, I brought the one you reserved.
いちちゃん、予約してたやつ持ってきたよ
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Was 2 adults enough?
大人2枚で合ってた?
It matched.
合ってた
Because it wasn't just one child.
子供1枚じゃなかったから
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Yeah, thank you.
うん、ありがとう
go?
行く?
There are cherry blossoms.
桜ある
It's true!
本当だ!
Oh no, it suits you too much.
やばい、似合いすぎ
It's super cute.
超かわいいじゃん
It's so cute right now.
めちゃめちゃかわいいじゃん、今の
Is it that time already?
もうそんな時期だっけ?
Is it early, March?
早いんだ、3月?
March, right?
3月か、そうだよね
Good to see you.
見れたね、よかった
I want to see this face even after mid-April.
4月中旬以降も見たいけどな、この顔
Will you come again?
もう 一 回 来る?
Should I watch it again?
もう一回見ようかな
amazing.
すごい
Hey, Miki-chan.
ね え、みきちゃん
Let's ride this.
これ乗ろう
boat?
ボート?
copper?
どう?
Let's ride.
乗ろうよ
There are two of them.
なんか2個あるよ
what?
何?
Two pieces.
2個って
Low boat, cycle boat.
ローボート、サイクルボート
Which one is better?
どっちがいいかな?
Miki-chan is the better one.
みきちゃんがいい方
Let's do it this way.
こっちにしよう
Should I do it this way?
こっちにする?
Okay.
いいよ
A foot pedal?
足こぐやつ?
A foot pedal guy.
足こぐやつ
You were trying to have a little fun.
ちょっと楽しようとしたでしょ
It's obvious though.
バレバレなんですけど
Is this your first time?
こういうの初めて?
It's my first time.
初めてよ
Hey, turn the steering wheel properly.
ほら、ちゃんとハンドル切って
You like cars, right?
車好きでしょ?
I like cars.
車好き
Meki-chan is good at driving.
めきちゃんって車運転上手なんだ
Are you good at it?
上手かな?
perhaps.
多分
TRUE?
本当?
It's rare for a girl to like cars.
女の子が車好きって珍しいじゃん
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
I like it.
好きだよ
Let's go on a drive date next time.
今度ドライブデートしようよ
Well then.
じゃあ
Well, let's go to the cafe where Miki-chan works.
じゃあ、みきちゃんの働いてるカフェ行って、
After that, we had a driving date, and then we rode this one more time.
その後ドライブデートして、その後もう一回これに乗る
I'll ride this again.
もう一回これに乗る
That's right.
アリだね
Are you driving properly?
ちゃんと運転してる?
Is it done?
できてる?
I also have to hold the steering wheel properly.
俺もちゃんとハンドル握らないと
what?
何?
Stop it.
やめてよ
why?
なんで?
It's outside.
外じゃん
It's really outside.
めっちゃ外じゃん
But outside.
外だけど
It’s dangerous, it’s dangerous, it’s dangerous.
やばいやばいやばいやばい
This is seriously dangerous.
マジでやばい
Handle properly?
ちゃんとハンドル?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Miki-chan, come on, show me your breasts.
みきちゃん、ちょっとさ、ここでおっぱい見せて
See you then.
じゃあな
show me.
見せて
Okay, show me.
いいから見せて
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Delicious.
う まい
TRUE?
本当?
Money, right?
金よね
This is amazing, so erotic.
すごいな、エロいなこれ
No, no, no.
だめだめ
Show me a little more.
もうちょっと見せて
please.
お願い
Wow that's amazing.
うわーすげー
I can't stand it.
たまんねー
Seriously.
マジで
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
this.
これ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Just take off your pants for a moment.
ちょっとこのままパンツ脱いで
Take it off.
脱いで
please.
お願い
There are so many people.
めっちゃ人いるよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
There are so many people.
めっちゃ人いるじゃん
But from that distance, wouldn't you be able to see it?
でもあの距離からだったらさ、見えなくない?
Here are the pants.
ここでパンツは
You'll never see it.
決して見えないよね
Can't you see it?
見えないかな
I'll definitely come though.
めっちゃ来るけど
Then face forward?
じゃあ正面向く?
It would be bad if it was on the side.
横だとまずいよね
appear?
見える?
Well, it's okay.
まあでも、まあいいか
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
If it felt like this.
この感じだったら
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Take it off a little.
ちょっと脱いで
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Take it off.
脱いで
Are you okay
大丈夫
kana?
かな?
It's okay.
大丈夫 だって
Just pants.
パンツだけ
Then I'll come along.
じゃあ俺こいでおくから
I'll come by.
こいでおくから
Oh my God.
あーやば
Yay ba.
やーば
Which which one?
どれどれどれ
It's like this.
こんな感じ
Show me well.
よく見せて
Turn over the spurt.
スパートめくって
Seriously.
マジやば
It's kind of moist.
なんかしっとりしてる
It's really moist.
めっちゃしっとりしてる
what happened?
どうしたの?
Wow.
うわー
Was it inside the mancon?
マンコンの中あったか
It's really warm.
めちゃめちゃあったかいよ
Also, let's go somewhere more comfortable together.
あとさ、もっと2人で落ち着けれるとこ行く?
Where can I calm down?
落ち着けるとこ?
good?
いい?
Is it okay?
いいんちゃう?
I left Pracho there.
プラチョ置いてんじゃん
morning
早
stomach.
い
Tsk tsk.
ち っくり
Chick
ちっく
It's fixed.
り 固まってる
squeeze.
絞る
It's beautiful.
綺麗じゃん
Can't drink?
飲めないちゃった?
I couldn't drink it.
飲めないちゃった
This is a tea bag.
これティーバックなんだよね
Everything is shown.
全部映ってる
It's quite embarrassing.
結構恥ずかしい
Point the push hole this way.
押し穴こっち向けて
In bed.
寝むじになって
Sleeping.
寝むじ
This is it.
これなんだよ
It's medium-shabby.
中ビシャビシャじゃん
Bisha
ビシャ
Bisha.
ビ シャ
I'm starting to feel like going again.
また行きそうになってきた
I want you to do it while sitting.
ジンジン座りながらしてほしいな
It's going to be exciting there too.
そこでもジンジンになるよ
Further down.
もっと下
Can I come in?
入 れてもいい?
I fell asleep.
寝ちゃったね
I have multiple duties
掛け持っちゃ
Even though it was, it came together like this.
った のにこうやって合体しちゃうのに
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
like?
好き?